Charles Mingus Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-44)
  - Manuscript Music (Box 1-29, Box 32-44)
    - Original Music Manuscripts (Box 1-28, Box 32-44)
      - Bill's song / lyrics by Charles Mingus; music by Paul M. Jeffrey., Lead sheet; 2 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript.; Access points: Jeffrey, Paul M. Mingus, Charles (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Bird calls., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 127. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Black saint and the sinner lady. See also: Soul fusion, Full score; 57 p.; various sizes.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 131. (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Black saint and the sinner lady. See also: Soul fusion, Full score; [59] leaves; 33 x 26.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph score in pencil, with annotations in red pencil.; Reference no.: 131. (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Black saint and the sinner lady. See also: Soul fusion, Full score; 57 p.; 28 x 21.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph score in pencil.; Reference no.: 131. (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Black saint and the sinner lady. See also: Soul fusion, Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 131. (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Black saint and the sinner lady. See also: Soul fusion, Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 28.5 cm.; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscripts.; Reference no.: 131. (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Black stome 10:30., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. At bottom: Piano score for untitled piece. On verso: Chord scheme for the piece "Sweet". (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Blue cee., Baritone sax part; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. On verso: Reincarnation of a lovebird.; Reference no.: 227. (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Blue cee., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscripts. At bottom of first p.: © January 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc.; Reference no.: 227. (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Blue tide., Trumpet part; 1 p.; 31 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no: 243. (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Blues Ballard., Instrumental part; 1 p.; 15 x 24.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink and red pencil. At head: A-167. (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Blues for some bones., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © December, 1976, Jazz Workshop, Inc. (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Blues [in F]., Trombone part; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. On verso: Untitled piece for trombone. (Box-folder 3/12)
      - Body., Full score; 4 p.; 27 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Boogie stop shuffle., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink on transparent paper. On bottom: © December, 1950, Jazz Workshop, Inc.; Reference no.: 220. (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Boogie stop shuffle / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 11 leaves; 28 x 43 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 006.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 32/8)
      - Boppin' in Boston., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 130. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Bus voice., Full score; 12 leaves; 30.5 x 41 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 121. (Box-folder 32/9)
      - But you., Full score; 5 leaves; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 138. (Box-folder 3/16)
      - Cabin see: Winds
      - Canon., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript. (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Carolyn "Keki" Mingus., Condensed score; 2 leaves; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc. 1977.; Reference no.: 119. (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Carolyn "Keki" Mingus., Full score; 10 leaves; 39 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 007, 119. (Box-folder 43/1)
      - Carolyn "Keki" Mingus., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 007. (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Celia (chords)., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 30.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil and ink. At head: Roberto Laueri [sic]. At bottom, note to Roberto: "Never write 8th notes trip's in N.Y.C. ..." (Box-folder 4/3)
      - Celia., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 131. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Celia., Chord chart; 1 p.; 31 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Celia (chord progressions)., Chord charts; 7 leaves; 28 cm.; Note: Manuscripts in pencil. This material appears to be graded classroom assignments. (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Celia., Instrumental parts; 14 leaves; 32 cm.; Note: Copyists' manuscripts in pencil and ink. Verso of drum part: Canon II in pencil. Folder includes photocopies. (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Celia., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil. Verso of baritone saxophone part: Diane and Peggy's ________ Skylight. Folder includes photocopies of parts. (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Cell block F is Nazi U.S.A. see: Jive five floor four
      - Chair in the sky / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 19 leaves; 28 x 43 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 010.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 32/10)
      - Chazzenova., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © January, 1977, Jazz Workshop, Inc. (Box-folder 4/9)
      - The chill of death., Full score; 38 leaves in 2 folders; 53.5 cm.; Note: Deshan (thermofax) copy of copyist's manuscript.; Reference no.: 274. (Box-folder 43/2-3)
      - Clark in the dark., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 134. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Cleaner from Des Moines see: Dry cleaner from Des Moines
      - The clown., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscripts. At bottom: © January, 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc. (Box-folder 4/11)
      - The clown / Jaki Byard, arr., Instrumental parts with narration; pagination varies; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopies of copyist's manuscripts; narrative text on separate page.; Access points: Byard, Jaki (Box-folder 4/12)
      - The clown's afraid too., Instrumental parts (trumpet 1 and French horn parts only); pagination varies; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink with pencil markings. (Box-folder 4/13)
      - The clown's afraid too, [don't be afraid]. See also: Don't be afraid, the clown's afraid too, Condensed score; 4 leaves; 39.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 117. (Box-folder 32/11)
      - The clown's afraid too (don't be afraid)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyists' manuscripts in ink with pencil and ink markings.; Reference no.: 161. (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Color blind., Full score (incomplete); 1 p.; 28 x 35.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Come Sunday., Chord chart; 1 p.; 28 x 35.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink. (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Compositional theme story., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., November, 1976. (Box-folder 4/17)
      - Confucius says., Instrumental part; 1 p.; 27 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. On verso an untitled holograph score in pencil. (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Consider me., Lead sheet; 2 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. (Box-folder 4/19)
      - The critic - string quartet., Full score; 1 p.; 39.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 187. (Box-folder 32/12)
      - Cro-Magnum nights., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. On verso: instrumental part for Portrait; holograph in ink. (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Cryin' blues., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © December 1976, Jazz Workshop, Inc. (Box-folder 4/21)
      - Cumbia and jazz fusion., Condensed score; 16 leaves; 32 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph signed by Mingus in ink. (Box-folder 4/22)
      - Cumbia and jazz fusion., Instrumental parts; Note: Copyist's ms. in ink with annotations. (Box-folder 4/23)
      - Cumbia and jazz fusion., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink and pencil. (Box-folder 4/24)
      - Dark lightings., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil and crayon. (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Depressions., Full score (incomplete); 3 leaves; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Detour minus that dead end., Sketches; 2 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. On verso: Heavenly marriage. (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Devil., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink. On verso: Fascination. (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Devil is a woman., Full score; 2 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Devil woman., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 34.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © December 1976, Jazz Workshop, Inc.; Reference no.: 123. (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Devil woman., Full score; 6 leaves; 30.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil and ink.; Reference no.: 123. (Box-folder 32/13)
      - Devil woman., Condensed score sketch; 2 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 123. (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Devil woman., Trumpet II part; 2 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 123. (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Diane., Full score; 3 leaves; 28 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil.; Reference no.: 114. (Box-folder 32/14)
      - Diane see: Mingus dance no. 7
      - Dianeland see: Mingus dance no. 7
      - Dizzy moods. See also: Mingus dance no. 6, Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of manuscript. At bottom: © Jan. 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc., Los Angeles, California.; Reference no.: 252. (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Dizzy profile., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Holographs in pencil and ink.; Reference no.: 015. (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Don't be afraid, the clown's afraid too., Lead sheet; 2 leaves; 27.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph.; Reference no.: 016, 117, 143, 161. (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Don't be afraid, the clown's afraid too., Instrumental parts; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink with pencil markings; Reference no.: 016 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Don't be afraid, the clown's afraid too., Full score; 35 p.; 27.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript.; Reference no.: 016. (Box-folder 32/15)
      - Don't be afraid, the clown's afraid too / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; [48] p.; 36.5 x 43 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson; includes photocopies.; Reference no.: 143.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 43/4)
      - Don't be afraid, the clown's afraid too (#13) / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 27 leaves; 35.5 x 43 cm.; Note: Photocopy of manuscript by Sy Johnson with markings in ink.; Reference no.: 016.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 32/16)
      - Don't let it happen here (from "I Am the Guilty")., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Holographs in pencil and ink.; Reference no.: 164. (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Dream of my girl., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. (Box-folder 5/14)
      - [Dry] cleaner from Des Moines / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 10 leaves; 28 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 011.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 32/17)
      - Duke Ellington's sound of love., Instrumenal parts; pagination varies; 31.5 cm. [December, 1974].; Note: Copyists' manuscripts in ink. Includes photocopies of tenor sax part and piano-vocal score.; Reference no.: 022. (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Duke's choice., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 29.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. (Box-folder 5/16)
      - E.S.P. See also: Extrasensory perception See also: Mind-readers convention, Lead sheet; 1 p.; 29.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 140. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. (Box-folder 5/17)
      - E's flat, Ah's flat too (#21)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 2 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink and pencil. (Box-folder 5/18)
      - East coasting (a.k.a. "51st Street blues")., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. (Box-folder 5/19)
      - East coasting., Instrumental part; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Holographs in pencil. (Box-folder 5/20)
      - Eat that chicken., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © February, 1976, Jazz Workshop, Inc., New York, NY. (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Ecclusiastics., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscripts. (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Ecclusiastics / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 16 leaves; 35.5 x 43 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson.; Reference no.: 151.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 32/18)
      - Ecclusiastics (#3)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink; includes photocopies.; Reference no.: 018. (Box-folder 6/3)
      - [Eclipse]., Lead sheet; 2 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink with holograph pencil markings. On verso: Lead line with lyrics.; Reference nos.: 019, 020, 141, 288. (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Eclipse., Lead sheet, lyrics included; 1 p.; 19 x 23.5 cm.; Note: Holographs in pencil. In upper-right corner: "Celia Mingus - Chas Mingus".; Reference nos.: 019, 020, 141, 288. (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Eclipse., Lead sheet, lyrics included (incomplete); 2 p.; 30.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference nos.: 019, 020, 141, 288. (Box-folder 6/6)
      - Eclipse., Lead sheets, 2 versions; 1 + 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Manuscripts in ink by Andrew Homzy. Version I includes melody line, chord progressions, and lyrics. Handwritten note at bottom dated: 26 Feb. '87. Version II includes melody line and chord progressions only.; Reference nos.: 019, 020, 141, 288. (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Eclipse., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript. At bottom: © January, 1975, Jazz Workshop, Inc., Los Angeles, California.; Reference nos.: 019, 020, 141, 288. (Box-folder 6/8)
      - Eclipse., Condensed score; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph.; Reference nos.: 019, 020, 141, 288. (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Eclipse., Full score; 3 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 141. (Box-folder 6/10)
      - Eclipse., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 30.5 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 141. (Box-folder 6/11)
      - Eclipse., Miscellaneous instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs and copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil; includes photocopies with holograph markings in ink and pencil. Laid in: Handwritten note by Andrew Homzy titled "Note for Eclipse 26/Feb/87".; Reference no.: 288. (Box-folder 6/12)
      - Eclipse (#10)., Full score; 9 p.; 28 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of copyist's manuscript.; Reference no.: 019. (Box-folder 33/1)
      - Eclipse (#10)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 30.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 019. (Box-folder 6/13)
      - Eclipse / Sy Johnson, arr., Full score; 7 leaves; 36 x 42.5 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Sy Johnson. Dated 1-29-72.; Access points: Johnson, Sy (Box-folder 33/2)
      - Enchantment., Full score; 6 leaves; 30.5 x 40.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 113. (Box-folder 33/3)
      - Enchantment., Instrumental parts; 9 lvs; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink.; Reference no.: 113. (Box-folder 6/14)
      - Epitaph., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 29.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 139. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music.; Reference no.: 256. (Box-folder 6/15)
      - Epitaph., Instrumental parts (reeds and brass); pagination varies; 32.5 cm. (2 folders).; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink.; Reference no.: 025. (Box-folder 6/16-17)
      - Epitaph (main score)., Full score; 40 leaves; 52.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil with holograph markings in colored pencil. Measures 1-199.; Reference no.: 256. (Box-folder 33/4)
      - Epitaph (main score)., Full score; 40 leaves; 52.5 cm. (2 folders); Note: Deshan (thermofax) copy of holograph score in pencil (33/1). Measures 1-199.; Reference no.: 256. (Box-folder 33/5-6)
      - Epitaph (#2)., Full score; 40 leaves; various sizes.; Note: Holograph in pencil. Measures 180-355.; Reference no.: 257. (Box-folder 33/7)
      - Epitaph (#3): started melody., Full score; 36 leaves; various sizes.; Note: Holograph in pencil. Measures 356-701.; Reference no.: 258. (Box-folder 34/1)
      - Epitaph (#4)., Full score; 23 leaves; various sizes.; Note: Holograph in pencil. Measures 702-1000; measures 1001-1142 missing.; Reference no.: 259. (Box-folder 34/2)
      - Epitaph (#5): moods in mambo section., Full score; 16 leaves; 28 x 35.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil. Measures 1143-1267.; Reference no.: 260. (Box-folder 6/18)
      - Epitaph (#6)., Full score; 16 leaves; 28 x 35.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil. Measures 1268-1651.; Reference no.: 261. (Box-folder 6/19)
      - Epitaph (#6)., Full score; [48] leaves; 34.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. Measures 1268-1651.; Reference no.: 261. (Box-folder 34/3)
      - Epitaph (#7)., Full score; 29 leaves; 46 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. Measures 1652-1767.; Reference no.: 262. (Box-folder 34/4)
      - Epitaph (#8): Pinky don't come here for love man., Full score; 23 leaves; 34.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. Measures 1768-1951.; Reference no.: 263. (Box-folder 34/5)
      - Epitaph (#9): Pinky don't come here for love man (Section II)., Full score; [15] leaves; 47 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. Measures 1952-2019).; Reference no.: 264. (Box-folder 34/6)
      - Epitaph (#10)., Full score; [21] leaves; 47 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. Measures 2020-2137.; Reference no.: 265. (Box-folder 34/7)
      - Epitaph (#11): Peggy's blue skylight., Full score; [17] leaves; 49 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil. Measures 2138-2216.; Reference no.: 266. (Box-folder 35/1)
      - Epitaph (#12): Wolverine blues., Full score; 22 leaves; 53.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil. Measures 2217-2394.; Reference no.: 267. (Box-folder 35/2)
      - Epitaph (#13): Todeskalte (The chill of death)., Full socre; 11 leaves; 35.5 x 41 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. Measures 2395-2477).; Reference no.: 268. (Box-folder 35/3)
      - Epitaph (#14): Children's dream-search., Full score; 37 leaves; 46 cm.; Note: Manuscript in pencil by Gene Roland and Charles Mingus. Measures 2478-2684.; Reference no.: 269. (Box-folder 35/4)
      - Epitaph (#15)., Full score; 24 leaves; 54 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. Measures 2685-2762.; Reference no.: 270. (Box-folder 35/5)
      - Epitaph (#16)., Full score; 22 leaves; various sizes.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 271. (Box-folder XL/0)
      - Epitaph (#17): Noon night., Full score; 19 leaves; 46 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil. Measures 3370-3446.; Reference no.: 272. (Box-folder 35/6)
      - Eulogy for Rudy Williams., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © February, 1976, Jazz Workshop, Inc., New York, N.Y.; Reference no.: 170. (Box-folder 6/20)
      - Eulogy for Rudy Williams., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink. On verso of alto saxophone, tenor saxophone, piano, bass, and drums part is the tune Portrait II.; Reference no.: 170. (Box-folder 6/21)
      - Extrasensory perception (#12). See also: Mind-readers convention, Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Ozalid copies of copyists' manuscripts in ink with pencil markings.; Reference no.: 026. (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Fables of Faubus., Lead sheet; 3 leaves; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph.; Reference no.: 027. (Box-folder 7/2)
      - Fables of Faubus., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; various sizes.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil, photocopies of holographs, and copyists' manuscripts in ink. On verso of one part is the tune Koko.; Reference no.: 027. (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Far Wells, Mill Valley., Bass part; 4 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph.; Reference no.: 245. (Box-folder 7/4)
      - Farewell, Farwell: AKA last party., Lead sheet; 1 lv.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 110. (Box-folder 7/5)
      - [Farwell farewell]., Piano sketch; 2 p.; 31 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 028. (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Farwell farewell., Full score; 1 leaf; 39 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 028. (Box-folder 43/5)
      - Farwell, farewell [a.k.a. Farwells Mill Valley]., Instrumental parts; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 028. (Box-folder 7/7)
      - [Farwell farewell]: written "Farwell fairwell"., Trombone part; 3 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink with pencil markings. Note at head: Does not match other parts - A.[?].; Reference no.: 029. (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Fascination., Guitar part; 2 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in ink and pencil.; On verso: the tune Love nest crossed out. (Box-folder 7/9)
      - The Fess Williams soul., Full score; 8 leaves; 34.5 x 43.5 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscript in pencil.; Reference no.: 111. (Box-folder 36/1)
      - The Fess Williams soul., Full score; 8 leaves; 35 x 43 cm.; Note: Deshan (thermofax) copy of copyist's manuscript (Ref. no. 111).; Reference no.: 285. (Box-folder 36/2)
      - Flamingo., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink and pencil.; On verso: Diatonic chords. (Box-folder 7/10)
      - Folk forms #1., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., November, 1976. (Box-folder 7/11)
      - Folk forms #2., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., November, 1976. (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Fool's passion., Instrumental part; 2 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. On verso: 2nd trumpet part for the tune Blue skies. (Box-folder 7/13)
      - For you., Guitar part; 1 p.; 34 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 7/14)
      - Four hands., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 35.5 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. At bottom: © Jazz Workshop, Inc., New York, New York, November 1975. (Box-folder 7/15)
      - Frank Maybry, Jr., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 32 cm.; Note: Copyist's manuscripts in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 030. (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Frankie and Johnny., Full score; 69 leaves; 31 cm.; Note: Holograph pencil.; Reference no.: 105. (Box-folder 7/17)
      - [Frankie and Johnny: 2nd Act]., Full score; 2 leaves; 31 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 105. (Box-folder 7/18)
      - Freedom., Full score; 11 leaves; 54 cm.; Note: Thermafax copy of copyist's manuscript.; Reference no.: 277. (Box-folder 36/3)
      - GG train., Lead sheet; 1 p.; 28 cm.; Note: Photocopy of holograph. Marked at head: 136. In typescript: Di Charles Mingus - Edizioni Blue Team Music. (Box-folder 7/19)
      - The glass enclosure., Bass part; 1 p.; 32 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil. (Box-folder 7/20)
      - God's portrait., Drum part; 1 p.; 31.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in ink. On verso: The habit. (Box-folder 7/21)
      - Gone with the wind., Condensed score; 1 p.; 27.5 cm.; Note: Holograph in pencil.; Reference no.: 201. (Box-folder 7/22)
      - Good-bye Eric (#8)., Instrumental parts; pagination varies; 30 cm.; Note: Holographs in ink and pencil.; Reference no.: 083. (Box-folder 7/23)